Ayesha Hamad . Jarvis Consulting

I have done BS in Computer Science and have 3 years of programming experience in C++ in mobile application development. I have also taken Full Stack Java Development Course from ComIT, Manitoba and Software Quality Assurance Course - Manual and Automation Teasting from JustWin, Ontario to upgrade my knowledge. To persue my career in Software Development and Testing feild I also took some certifications and I am Certified Automation Tester, SCRUM Tester and Manual Tester. What really excites me is that IT industry is ruling the world and I always wanted to be the part of it. I like to code and doing what you like most increases your creativity and productivity as well. I have excellent communication and interpersonal skills and always willing to learn new technologies and adapting new environment

Skills

Proficient: Java, C++, OOP, Data Structures, Linux/Bash, RDBMS/SQL, Agile/Scrum, SDLC, Git/GitHub

Competent: Test scripting using UFT (QTP), Selenium WebDriver (JAVA) implementing Page Object Model and

TestNG, ALM Octane (QC), Jira, Manual Testing

Familiar: Obj-C, C# .Net, Rest API, SOAP UI - Web Services, Web designing

Jarvis Projects

Project source code: https://github.com/jarviscanada/jarvis_data_eng_AyeshaHamad

Cluster Monitor [GitHub]: Add here detail

Core Java Apps [GitHub]:

• Twitter App:

• JDBC App:

• Grep App: Add here

Springboot App [GitHub]: Not Started

Python Data Analytics [GitHub]: Not Started

Hadoop [GitHub]: Not StartedSpark [GitHub]: Not Started

Cloud/DevOps [GitHub]: Not Started

Highlighted Projects

Web app for resturant: Suspendisse posuere luctus aliquet. Quisque magna tellus, tempor vitae arcu sed, volutpat scelerisque lacus. Aliquam varius pulvinar dapibus. Ut a tincidunt sem. Aenean sollicitudin fringilla erat ut imperdiet. Phasellus fermentum, enim vitae laoreet elementum, eros nisl hendrerit lorem.

Professional Experiences

Software Developer, Jarvis (2021-present): ADD HERE FURTHER DETAIL Suspendisse a tincidunt odio. Suspendisse posuere luctus aliquet. Quisque magna tellus, tempor vitae arcu sed, volutpat scelerisque lacus. Aliquam varius pulvinar dapibus. Ut a tincidunt sem. Aenean sollicitudin fringilla erat ut imperdiet. Phasellus fermentum, enim vitae laoreet elementum, eros nisl hendrerit lorem.

Software Engineer, FiveRivers Technologies, Lahore, Pakistan (2011-2014): Worked on Marmalade - a cross platform for mobile application development using C++ and developed android and IOS applications. My basic dedication was creating the Photo Editor app in pepper.pk integrating openCV and photo shop algorithms to create filters. Key Responsibilities: Created Photo Editor App using Marmalade, for android and IOS. Created android and IOS extensions to add monetization s and other SDKs to marmalade platform like Revmob, StartApp, Leadbolt, Google Ad mediation, Flurry, Crittercism using JNI, Java, Obj-C and marmalade EDK (extension development kit). Maintained existing programs by modifying as required and making the code reusable. Wrote, modified, integrated, and tested software code. Wrote test cases for each module to ensure a bug free and robust code. Gathered and Understood user requirements to develop logical specifications.

Education

Punjab University, Lahore, Pakistan (2007-2011), Bachelor of Science in Computer Science, College of Information and Technology

Com IT, Winnipeg, Canada (June 2018-Sep 2018), Full Stack Java Development, IT

Justwin IT Solutions, Brampton, Canada (Jan 2021-Apr 2021), Quality Assurance: Manual and Automation Testing, IT

Miscellaneous

- Endorsed Automation Tester Certification
- Endorsed Manual Tester Certification
- Endorsed Scrum Tester Certification